You can imagine I'm a silica--
oh, you got to pass this out.
I'm a big silicate,
an SiO4, and I'm
connected to these
other silicate groups
through this shared bridged
oxygen. And I'm a bulky thing,
and I'm trying to move around in
the liquid, crystal complexity.
I'm cooling down, and I'm
trying to move around.
And [INAUDIBLE] told
me to go that way,
but it's actually over there,
or there's no building there
and I don't know where to go.
Where is the lattice site?
It's complicated.
Glass could form.
Or maybe I'm a silicate
group and I'm like, hey,
could you please
get out of my way?
You're really
slowing things down,
you other silicate group
that I'm attached to.
Viscous, get out of my way.
No, I can't, viscous.
Or maybe you're a silicate
group and you're cooling down
and you're like,
that was very sudden.
I didn't even realize
that happened.
All of a sudden I'm
supposed to be a solid?
This is what's happening.
And so instead of getting into
this beautiful quartz crystal
it doesn't get there.
It doesn't get there.
A supercooled liquid
wants to be a solid.
It wants to, but it can't for
some reason, for some reason
that has to do with those.